Munseong Jeong (Leon)

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Profile

I have 1 years of front-end experience and familiar with HTML, CSS, JavaScript also experienced using numerous programming languages/tools including React, Typescript, NodeJs, MySQL, Git. During the university I also used Java, PHP, C++, C#, Python languages on assignment projects. I enjoy learning new languages and development techniques. Based on designer experience I am good to use of PS, Ai, Figma and AdobeXD tools. I am also adapt quickly to different working environments and I am a good team player that received many positive feedback from colleagues.

Employment History

FrontEnd Developer (volunteer), Trans Tasman Energy Group, Melbourne

MAY 2022 - PRESENT

TTEG is providing solutions of energy requirements for the large, small and medium businesses. Which using self developed customer management system.

My responsibilities were:

- Created Retailer, Company, Council and Association list and detail pages.
- Fetch the data from API then filter or sort them.
- Technologies used: React, Typescript, Material UI, Git, Bitbucket,
- Agile mode develop environment
- Deploy the website to the server.
- Use design tool to create the layout of the website.
- Communicated with customers to discuss their needs.

Rider Operations, EASI Australia Pty Ltd , Melbourne

OCTOBER 2019 - MARCH 2022

EASI Australia is a well-known international food delivery corporation.

My responsibilities were:

- managed about 200 riders in Australia to help the platform to improve order capacity;
- helped riders to solve different issues they have during work;
- solved the conflicts and communication problems among merchants, riders and customers:
- improved communication and teamwork skills.

Online Store Manager, DamingGlass Pty Ltd , South Korea

MAY 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2017

DamingGlass is a global trading company. The core business is the purchase, shipping, and sale of original glass sheets from China to Korea.

My responsibilities were:

- developed online shopping platform from scratch based on WordPress and Cafe24 to enable customers to order products and track orders online, mainly used PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript;
- managed product information on different e-commerce platforms, such as Naver shopping, Gmarket and 11 street store, including creating images via Photoshop

Details

CARLTON, 3000 Australia 0452462858 jmunseng@gmail.com

Links

Portfolio

LinkedIn

Github

Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript

React, TypeScript, SQL, Java, Oracle, MongoDB, Material UI, Git

Node.js, JQuery, Bootstrap, C, C#, Python

Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop,

Power BI & Tableau

Microsoft Office

Effective Time Management

Languages

English

Chinese

Korean

Hobbies

Pencil ketch, Pool ball

• translated documents between Chinese and Korean.

Web Designer, Sappira, South Korea

JULY 2013 - APRIL 2014

Sappira is a company that designs, produces, and sells clothing for medical and entertainment companies in Korea.

My responsibilities were:

- created and maintained promotion web pages, mainly used PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript;
- maintained product content across different online shopping platforms, including editing product information and creating photos via Photoshop

Front end Developer, KISKorea, South Korea

FEBRUARY 2012 - APRIL 2013

Kiskorea provides an online international tourism platform and a mobile gaming platform.

My responsibilities were:

- coded and maintained static web pages from the design, including both tourism and mobile gaming platforms' user interface pages and admin management pages, mainly based on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and W2UI;
- implemented functionalities that get data from database, mainly based on Java and MySQL;
- tested, debugged and fixed errors in web applications.

Education

React Development, General Assambly, Melbourne

MAY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

Bachelor of Information Technology, Deakin University, Melbourne

MARCH 2018 - NOVEMBER 2020

Obtained Average Distinction

Majors: Application Development

Graduate Certificate of Business Analytics, Kaplan Business School Australia, Melbourne

JULY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Majors: Business Analytics